Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and

Notice Period: 2 Months

Engineering]

Shyamal Naskar 🕡 Featured

Software Developer, Seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program MgmtRequirement Gathering, ETL, Toad, PLSQL, Data Modeling, Data Warehousing, Oracle, Oracle Data Integrator, ODI, Linux, Python, Snaplogic



Current Designation: Software Engineer

Current Company: Twopiradian info analytic Pvt Itd

Current Location: Kolkata

Pref. Location: Kolkata, Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, ETL, Toad, PLSQL, Data

Warehousing, Oracle, Oracle Data Integrator, ODI, Linux, Python, snaplogic

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 31-Oct-20 Last Modified: 31-Oct-20

Summary

Total 5 years of experience in IT.

1 year 9 months of experience in the area of MDM (Master Data Management) particularly Development in SQL (postgresql) and Designing of ETL (in Snaplogic).

3 years 3 months of experience in the area of Data Warehousing and Business Intelligence particularly Development in SQL, PL/SQL (ORACLE) and Designing of ETL (in ODI 12c).

Work Experience

Twopiradian info analytic Pvt Itd as Software Engineer

Jan 2019 to Till Date

Software Developer, Seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program MgmtRequirement Gathering, ETL, Toad, PLSQL, Data Modeling, Data Warehousing, Oracle, Oracle Data Integrator, ODI, Linux, Python, Snaplogic

British Telecom as Associate Software Engineer

Oct 2017 to Dec 2018

Have good knowledge in oracle PL-SQL. Load data form source(flat file, tables) to target table using ODI (ELT tool).

Ebiw info analytic Pvt ltd as Software Developer

Jun 2015 to Jul 2017

Have good knowledge in oracle PL-SQL. Load data form source(flat file, tables) to target table using ODI (ELT tool)

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Adamas Institute Of Technology in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
SQL, PL/SQL			4 Year(s)	
ORACLE 11g /12c				
WINDOWS SERVER, linux				
ODI	12c	2017	3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)	
Snaplogic		2020	1 Year(s) 10 Month(s)	
Python	3		8 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Bengali	Expert			
Hindi	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time